CHANGSIK WOO

• e-mail) jasoncswoo@gmail.com • tel) (+82) 010-8478-9023 • homepage) https://changsik-woo.github.io

RESEARCH INTERESTS

As an inspection process engineer at LG Display, I aim to build full inspection automation via AI. I am deeply interested in various research fields essential for making inspection process automated by using diverse types of images.

- Computer Vision & Image Processing
- Computational Photography
- Video / Multimodal Understanding

WORK EXPERIENCE

LG Display, Paju, South Korea

Jul 2016 - Present

Senior Engineer - WOLED(TV) Manufacture Inspection Process (Currently focused on Automation) Honors & Award : Selected as Core Employee (2023-present) & Degree Dispatcher (2024)

PROJECTS

Projects Related to Inspection Process Automation at LG Display,

- Mura Defect Detection Automation via Anomaly Detection (PaDiM) (Jul. 2023 Jun. 2024)
 - 1. [Feasibility Test] By using screen images, test involved Image Download, Image Processing, Training & Modeling, and Performance Verification.
 - 2. [Optimizing Image Processing] When taking images in the previous process, images may be rotated or curved due to many reasons. To improve this problem, a python module for image processing was developed. That module find edges through contour approximation, and rotation and curve are improved through perceptive transform. In conclusion, PaDiM accuracy is improved (OK: $11\% \rightarrow 69\%$, NG: $29\% \rightarrow 93\%$).
- Defect Classification Automation through Trained Classification Model (Jul. 2022 Dec. 2022)
 By using thumbnail images, classification model was trained and applied at inspection process to
 Classify different types of defect labels including over-detect. This model can be classified with 95% accuracy and over-detect can be improved by more than 70%

EDUCATION

Sungkyunkwan University, Suwon, South Korea

Mar 2010 - Aug 2016

B.S. in Electronic and Electric Engineering

GPA: 3.85 / 4.5

SKILLS

Languages: Python (Intermediate)